http://www.ronniecoleman.net/pages/privacy-policy

Cart
"Close Cart"
GENERAL
Ronnie Coleman Signature Series™ respects the privacy of every individual who visits our websites, responds to our interactive advertisements, or interacts with Ronnie Coleman Signature Series™ through the use of the web. This Privacy Statement outlines the information Ronnie Coleman Signature Series™ will collect and how we will use that information. This Statement will also instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visit Ronnie Coleman Signature Series™ websites.
PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATIONRonnie Coleman Signature Series™ will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (that is, your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. If you do not want your personally identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like for us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the email address listed at the bottom of this Statement. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files. When you do provide us with personally identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise: We may store and process that information to better understand your needs and how we can improve our products and services; we may use that information to contact you; and we may provide that information to third parties.
INDIVIDUALS UNDER 18This website is not intended for use by anyone under the age of eighteen. Ronnie Coleman Signature Series™ has no intention of collecting any personally identifiable information (that is, name, address, telephone number, or email address) from individuals under eighteen years of age. Where appropriate, Ronnie Coleman Signature Series™ will specifically instruct those under eighteen not to submit such information on our websites or advertisements. If an individual under eighteen has provided us with personally identifiable information, that person or a parent or guardian of that person should contact us at the email address listed at the bottom of this Statement if he or she would like this information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the under-aged individual's information from our existing files.
NON–PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLYIn some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the website from which you linked to our site or advertisement.
INFORMATION WE MAY PLACE AUTOMATICALLY ON YOUR COMPUTER'S HARD DRIVEWhen you view one of our websites or advertisements, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and will help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor a website or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
WHO TO CONTACTIf you have submitted personally identifiable information through a Ronnie Coleman Signature Series™ website or interactive advertisement, and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us at the email address or telephone number listed below. We will use reasonable efforts to delete this information from our existing files.
Further questions? Contact us at by phone at 1-888-854-3316 or by email at customerservice@ronniecoleman.net
Added to cart!
Cart
Total:
Your Order Ships for Free!
Free shipping on orders over XX
You Get Free Shipping at Checkout!
